<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Cirrane]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Cirrane</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:33:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:33:42 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Fire]]></title><description><![CDATA[Affinity
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self">
Rarity Common
Deity Pele
Vessel Cherry Fire is an element known to burn bright. It is not easy to contain, but with the right touch, fire can be warm and inviting. It can provide light in even the darkest places. Fire hungers for freedom. Too much freedom, however, and fire will consume everything in its path, but too little may cause it to lash out in unexpected ways. Fire affinities demand respect, but do not freely give it. They are known for having explosive personalities, but are passionate lovers, and loyal to those who have earned it.
Fire affinities are known for being passionate and fierce. They burn bright in everything they do and never falter no matter what life throws their way. Warm and inviting, fire affinities welcome all, and they are often viewed as ride or die for those that earn their loyalty. Never scorn a fire affinity, however, as they are said to be quick to anger and their fury leaves everlasting scars. The wrath of a fire affinity will take down all unfortunate enough to fall in their path and they will stop at nothing to get revenge. Fire affinities can not be control and are said to lash out against any who attempt to contain them. It take a gentle and patient touch to love and care for a fire affinity, but earn their loyalty and you will be great rewarded.
Body Temperature Manipulation The ability to manipulate the body temperature of oneself and/or others. Heat resistance. Fire Resistance The power to be highly resistant to fire. Fire Manipulation The power to manipulate fire. BEGINNER LEVEL - At the beginner level of fire manipulation, users can generate and control flames with basic proficiency. They can create small flames, manipulate their shape and size, and control the temperature of the fire. Users are able to ignite objects and produce simple fire-based attacks. They can control the heat intensity of the flames based on the impurities present in the materials being burned. However, their control over the flames may be somewhat limited, and they may struggle to maintain perfect control over the fire's movements and effects. Fire Manipulation The power to manipulate fire. INTERMEDIATE LEVEL - As users get to the medium level of fire manipulation, their abilities become more refined and versatile. They can generate larger flames and manipulate them with greater control. Users gain the ability to produce more complex fire-based attacks, such as fireballs, streams of flames, or fiery constructs. They can create defensive barriers of flames and control the spread of fire over a wider area. Additionally, users can enhance the intensity and heat of the flames, allowing them to inflict more damage and exert greater influence over their surroundings. Fire Manipulation The power to manipulate fire. ADVANCED LEVEL - At the master level of fire manipulation, users attain mastery over the element of fire, unlocking its full potential. They can manipulate flames with unlimited skill. Users gain the ability to produce extremely large and powerful flames, capable of engulfing and igniting entire areas or overwhelming multiple opponents simultaneously in flames. They can generate intense heat that can melt through even the most durable materials and cause a very devastating destruction. Users can manipulate the temperature of the flames at will, from searing heat to freezing cold, granting them supernatural control over the superpower of fire in most of its forms. In addition to their offensive capabilities. Fire Beam Emission The power to project beams of concentrated fire that burns anything upon contact. Fire Infusion The user can infuse objects (usually a weapon), beings or powers with fire, empowering and energizing them and allowing the user to manipulate their qualities and efficiency and even use fire in various ways to attack. Fire Barrier Generation Users can create walls of fire from nothing or by shaping existing fire into its desired shape. Walls generated by this power may or may not be immobile, and can be used both offensively and defensively. The ability to create shields out of fire. Firestorm Creation The power to create a terrifying inferno that incinerates all. Fire Aura The ability to surround oneself in fire. Fire Immunity The power to be completely unharmed by fire. Heat Immunity The power to be completely unharmed by heat. Absolute Burning The power to burn absolutely anything. ]]></description><link>00-wiki/magic/affinities/fire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Magic/Affinities/Fire.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:20:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="docs/05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="docs/05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sports Notes]]></title><link>03-notes/sports-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Sports Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:01:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Index]]></title><description><![CDATA[ Col <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Characters" data-href="Characters" href="00-wiki/characters.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="cm-iconize-icon" aria-label="LiIdCard" data-icon="LiIdCard" aria-hidden="true" style="display: inline-flex; transform: translateY(13%);"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="14px" height="14px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="lucide-id-card"><path d="M16 10h2"></path><path d="M16 14h2"></path><path d="M6.17 15a3 3 0 0 1 5.66 0"></path><circle cx="9" cy="11" r="2"></circle><rect x="2" y="5" width="20" height="14" rx="2"></rect></svg></span> Characters</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Timeline" data-href="Timeline" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="cm-iconize-icon" aria-label="LiClock" data-icon="LiClock" aria-hidden="true" style="display: inline-flex; transform: translateY(13%);"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="14px" height="14px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="lucide-clock"><circle cx="12" cy="12" r="10"></circle><polyline points="12 6 12 12 16 14"></polyline></svg></span> Timeline</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Stories" data-href="Stories" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="cm-iconize-icon" aria-label="LiBook" data-icon="LiBook" aria-hidden="true" style="display: inline-flex; transform: translateY(13%);"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="14px" height="14px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="lucide-book"><path d="M4 19.5v-15A2.5 2.5 0 0 1 6.5 2H19a1 1 0 0 1 1 1v18a1 1 0 0 1-1 1H6.5a1 1 0 0 1 0-5H20"></path></svg></span> Stories</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magic" data-href="Magic" href="00-wiki/magic/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="cm-iconize-icon" aria-label="LiStars" data-icon="LiStars" aria-hidden="true" style="display: inline-flex; transform: translateY(13%);"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="14px" height="14px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="lucide-stars"><path d="M9.937 15.5A2 2 0 0 0 8.5 14.063l-6.135-1.582a.5.5 0 0 1 0-.962L8.5 9.936A2 2 0 0 0 9.937 8.5l1.582-6.135a.5.5 0 0 1 .963 0L14.063 8.5A2 2 0 0 0 15.5 9.937l6.135 1.581a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .964L15.5 14.063a2 2 0 0 0-1.437 1.437l-1.582 6.135a.5.5 0 0 1-.963 0z"></path><path d="M20 3v4"></path><path d="M22 5h-4"></path><path d="M4 17v2"></path><path d="M5 18H3"></path></svg></span> Magic</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Locations" data-href="Locations" href="00-wiki/locations/locations.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="cm-iconize-icon" aria-label="LiMapPin" data-icon="LiMapPin" aria-hidden="true" style="display: inline-flex; transform: translateY(13%);"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="14px" height="14px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="lucide-map-pin"><path d="M20 10c0 4.993-5.539 10.193-7.399 11.799a1 1 0 0 1-1.202 0C9.539 20.193 4 14.993 4 10a8 8 0 0 1 16 0"></path><circle cx="12" cy="10" r="3"></circle></svg></span> Locations</a> ]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Index.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 01:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[
YOU CANNOT REVIVE THE DEAD.
YOU CANNOT SEEK IMMORTALITY.
YOU CANNOT CONTROL OR ALTER ANOTHER'S SOUL. Water Fire Air &amp; Earth
Refers to elemental magic.
Pure energy is a relatively new concept. Older generations struggle to accept this recent discovery.
Pure energy is the raw energy that connects the four together.
Body Mind &amp; Soul
Refers to spiritual magic.
This magic manifests through one's aura and spiritual energy. Crystals allow the user to go up a tier in their abilities while the crystal is in use. The more crystals are person has the high tier they become. Using too many crystals, however, can result in some sort of kickback/detriment to the user. Are crystals sort of like drugs in the idea of users becoming addicted to the power? Can they go through withdrawal symptoms from being cut off suddenly? Is this part of the reason crystals are regulated? ]]></description><link>00-wiki/magic/magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Magic/Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Old World]]></title><link>00-wiki/history/the-old-world.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/History/The Old World.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Esterran Rebellion]]></title><link>00-wiki/history/the-esterran-rebellion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/History/The Esterran Rebellion.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Body: Vyscera
Soul: Kamali
Mind: Mnemosyne
Fire: Pele
Water: Siren
Air: Pavana
Earth: Gaia (?)Magic is made up of 3 component:
Crystals Crystals are found in nature and function as containers for magical elements. They are harvested from the mines of Esterra and shipped off to factories for refinement and to be charged with magical energy for use.
They function as the batteries of this universe/act as a magic amplifier Runes Crystals can't function without the use of runes. Runes act as the circuitry of crystals and imbue crystals with a given element. Runes are carved into crystals with attributes/components of an element in order for the crystal to become charged with that element. EX: Fire for fire, water for water, etc. Innate Magic All humans (and animals?) are born with innate magic known as an affinity. This allows them to wield magic without the need for crystals/enhancers. Their magic will not be as strong without conduits but they may become stronger through years of studying and honing their abilities. Animals do have a form of passive magic in regards to the different affinities. Like humans, they are limited to 1 of the 7 elements. Their magic is passive, not active (ex: they can't breath fire, walk on water, etc.). How this manifests and what it looks like will be handled on a case by case basis and as needed to fit stories. Affinities have been broken down into tiers as outlined below to denote what a person may or may not be capable of. The use of crystals will bump a person up a tier and allow them to use stronger magic than before.do Tier 1 and 2 abilities, but a Tier 1 can’t do Tier 2 abilities. Tier 1 - Casual <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" target="_self">Body Temperature Manipulation</a> - The ability to manipulate the body temperature of oneself and/or others. Heat resistance.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Resistance" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Resistance" target="_self">Fire Resistance</a> - The power to be highly resistant to fire. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" target="_self">Fire Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate fire. BEGINNER LEVEL - At the beginner level of fire manipulation, users can generate and control flames with basic proficiency. They can create small flames, manipulate their shape and size, and control the temperature of the fire. Users are able to ignite objects and produce simple fire-based attacks. They can control the heat intensity of the flames based on the impurities present in the materials being burned. However, their control over the flames may be somewhat limited, and they may struggle to maintain perfect control over the fire's movements and effects. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" target="_self">Fire Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate fire. INTERMEDIATE LEVEL - As users get to the medium level of fire manipulation, their abilities become more refined and versatile. They can generate larger flames and manipulate them with greater control. Users gain the ability to produce more complex fire-based attacks, such as fireballs, streams of flames, or fiery constructs. They can create defensive barriers of flames and control the spread of fire over a wider area. Additionally, users can enhance the intensity and heat of the flames, allowing them to inflict more damage and exert greater influence over their surroundings. Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Manipulation" target="_self">Fire Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate fire. ADVANCED LEVEL - At the master level of fire manipulation, users attain mastery over the element of fire, unlocking its full potential. They can manipulate flames with unlimited skill. Users gain the ability to produce extremely large and powerful flames, capable of engulfing and igniting entire areas or overwhelming multiple opponents simultaneously in flames. They can generate intense heat that can melt through even the most durable materials and cause a very devastating destruction. Users can manipulate the temperature of the flames at will, from searing heat to freezing cold, granting them supernatural control over the superpower of fire in most of its forms. In addition to their offensive capabilities. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Beam_Emission" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Beam_Emission" target="_self">Fire Beam Emission</a> - The power to project beams of concentrated fire that burns anything upon contact. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Infusion" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Infusion" target="_self">Fire Infusion</a> - The user can infuse objects (usually a weapon), beings or powers with fire, empowering and energizing them and allowing the user to manipulate their qualities and efficiency and even use fire in various ways to attack. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Wall_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Wall_Generation" target="_self">Fire Barrier Generation</a> -Users can create walls of fire from nothing or by shaping existing fire into its desired shape. Walls generated by this power may or may not be immobile, and can be used both offensively and defensively. The ability to create shields out of fire. Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Firestorm_Creation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Firestorm_Creation" target="_self">Firestorm Creation</a> - The power to create a terrifying inferno that incinerates all.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Aura" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Aura" target="_self">Fire Aura</a> - The ability to surround oneself in fire.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Immunity" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Fire_Immunity" target="_self">Fire Immunity</a> - The power to be completely unharmed by fire. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Heat_Immunity" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Heat_Immunity" target="_self">Heat Immunity </a>- The power to be completely unharmed by heat. God <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Burning/Absolute" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Burning/Absolute" target="_self">Absolute Burning</a> - The power to burn absolutely anything. Unlisted Tier 1 - Casual <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" target="_self">Body Temperature Manipulation</a> - The ability to manipulate the body temperature of oneself and/or others. Cold Resistance.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing" target="_self">Freezing</a> - The power to decrease the thermal energy of liquids causing them to become solid. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" target="_self">Water Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate water. BEGINNER LEVEL - At the "beginner" level of water manipulation, users can control and possibly generate water with a basic degree of proficiency. They can form small spouts and geysers, manipulate their shape and size, and control their water's temperature with moderate precision (possibly dependent on the presence of impurities within the water). Users are capable of producing simple water-based attacks in the form of waves and streams. However, their control over the movements and properties of water may be somewhat limited in scope, making it challenging to maintain perfect control. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Walking" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Walking" target="_self">Water Walking</a> - The power to walk and/or run on the surface of the water. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" target="_self">Water Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate water. INTERMEDIATE LEVEL - As users progress to the "intermediate" level of water manipulation, their abilities grow more refined, versatile, and larger in scale. They can generate large waves and manipulate them with greater control. Users gain the ability to create more complex water-based attacks, such as larger waves, streams of water, or constructs of condensed water. They can conjure defensive water barriers and control the spread of water over a wider area. Additionally, they can enhance the intensity (heat and pressure) of the water, allowing them to inflict more damage and exert a greater influence over their surroundings. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Cutting" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Cutting" target="_self">Water Cutting</a> - The ability to use water to cut and pierce objects. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Healing_Water" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Healing_Water" target="_self">Healing Water</a> - The ability to heal by using water.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Boundary" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Boundary" target="_self">Water Boundary</a> - The ability to separate water from anything and everything else. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing_Touch" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing_Touch" target="_self">Freezing Touch</a> - The power to freeze through physical touch. Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Manipulation" target="_self">Water Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate water. ADVANCED LEVEL - At this level, total "mastery" over the water element is achieved, unlocking the element's full potential in all three forms: liquid, solid, and gas. The user can manipulate water with exceptional precision, alter its properties at will, and produce extremely large and powerful tidal waves/tsunamis capable of flooding large areas and/or overwhelming huge swathes of enemies even on dry land. Users can generate massive waves to crash down upon targets, causing extensive destruction, or bring forth enough water to completely change the terrain, transforming barren wastelands into small oceans. The amount of water controlled may range from lakefuls to entire oceanfuls, or even cover the whole planet's hydrosphere for users with supreme levels of mastery, making them akin to living natural disasters. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Beam_Emission" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Beam_Emission" target="_self">Water Beam Emission </a> - The power to project beams of compressed water. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Mimicry" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Mimicry" target="_self">Water Mimicry</a> - The power to transform into or have a physical body made up of water. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Wall_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Wall_Generation" target="_self">Water Barrier Generation</a> - The ability to create, summon, or generate walls by using water. The power to create shields out of water. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Sense" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Water_Sense" target="_self">Water Sense</a> - The user can perceive the movement in/on a body of water with extreme accuracy and determine where threats are placed in water sources. They can even understand the size of targets in water by perceiving the waves interfering with certain movements of bodies of water. Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Cold_Immunity" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Cold_Immunity" target="_self">Cold Immunity</a> - The power to be completely unharmed by cold.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Absolute_Zero_Inducement" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Absolute_Zero_Inducement" target="_self">Absolute Zero Inducement </a>- The power to induce absolute zero temperatures. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Frostbite_Inducement" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Frostbite_Inducement" target="_self">Frostbite Inducement</a> - The user can cause frostbite, freezing any part of an entity's body where one can turn the tissues and flesh into solid ice making the victim shatter into pieces due to freeze drying or cause a swelling making it hard to move for the victim. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_Creation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_Creation" target="_self">Blizzard Creation</a> - The ability to create snowstorms. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tidal_Wave_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tidal_Wave_Generation" target="_self">Tidal Wave Generation</a> - The ability to generate tidal waves. God <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Ocean_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Ocean_Manipulation" target="_self">Ocean Manipulation </a> - The power to manipulate the oceans and everything in them.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing/Absolute" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Freezing/Absolute" target="_self">Absolute Freezing</a> - The power to freeze absolutely anything. Unlisted Tier 1 - Casual <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" target="_self">Earth Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate earth. BEGINNER LEVEL - At the beginner level of earth manipulation, users can generate and control earth with basic proficiency. They can create small termors, manipulate their shape and size, and control the size of the amount of earth. Users are able to extracted boulders from the ground and produce simpleearth-based attacks. . However, their control over the earth may be somewhat limited, and they may struggle to maintain perfect control over the earths's movements and effects. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Seismic_Sense" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Seismic_Sense" target="_self">Seismic Sense</a> - The power to sense and perceive vibrations in the earth. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" target="_self">Earth Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate earth. INTERMEDIATE LEVEL - As users get to the medium level of earth manipulation, their abilities become more refined and versatile. They can generate larger amounts of earth and manipulate them with greater control. Users gain the ability to produce more complex earth-based attacks, such as boulders, streams of earth, or earth constructs. They can create defensive barriers of earth and control the spread of earth over a wider area. Additionally, users can enhance the intensity of the earth and are able to set off earthquakes, tear holes in the ground, allowing them to inflict more damage and exert greater influence over their surrounding <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Manipulation" target="_self">Plant Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate plants. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Empathy" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Empathy" target="_self">Plant Empathy</a> - The power to sense the overall well-being and conditions of plants.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Growth" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Growth" target="_self">Plant Growth</a> - The power to influence the growth of plant life.
Terra-kinesis - The power to manipulate gravity/magnetism &amp; magnetic fields. Grant the user the ability to move, manipulate, or otherwise interact with objects by controlling the gravity surrounding it. Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Manipulation" target="_self">Earth Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate earth. ADVANCED LEVEL - At the master level of earth manipulation, users attain mastery over the element of earth , unlocking its full potential. They can manipulate earth with unlimited skill. Users gain the ability to produce extremely large and powerful geologic material, capable of engulfing entire areas or overwhelming multiple opponents simultaneously in rock. They can generate intense earthquakes that can cause a very devastating destruction. Users is able to set off earthquakes, tear holes in the ground, carve slabs of stone and rock from geologic sources like mountains, crags and walls, shift the terrain around them, slice through stone with their mere fingertips, and control seismic energy. In addition to their offensive capabilities. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Wall_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earth_Wall_Generation" target="_self">Earth Barrier Generation</a> - The ability to create, summon, or generate walls by using earth. The ability to create shields out of earth. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Defense" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Defense" target="_self">Plant Defense</a> - The user possesses defensive skills that are enhanced by plant-based powers, allowing them to block, parry, dodge, reflect, etc. with the power of plant life. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Erosion_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Erosion_Manipulation" target="_self">Erosion Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate erosion and weathering. Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Enhancement" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Plant_Enhancement" target="_self">Plant Enhancement</a> - Power to augment, grow or bring plants back to life and even create them. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Geoscience" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Geoscience" target="_self">Geoscience</a> - The power to know everything about the earth and everything connected to it.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earthquake_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Earthquake_Generation" target="_self">Earthquake Generation</a> - The ability to create and cause powerful earthquakes. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Magma_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Magma_Manipulation" target="_self">Magma Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate lava and magma. God Earth Creation Caves, Valleys, Mountains, Canyons, Plains, etc. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tectonic_Plate_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tectonic_Plate_Manipulation" target="_self">Tectonic Plate Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate the tectonic plates under the planet's crust. Unlisted Tier 1 - Casual <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" target="_self">Air Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate air. BEGINNER LEVEL - At the beginner level of air manipulation, users can generate and control air with basic proficiency. They can create a small gust of wind, manipulate their shape and size, and control air temperature. Users can develop windstorms and produce simple air-based attacks. They can control the temperature of the air. However, their control over the air may be somewhat limited, and they may struggle to maintain perfect control over the air's movements and effects. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Walking" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Walking" target="_self">Air Walking </a>- The power to walk on air.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Atmospheric_Adaptation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Atmospheric_Adaptation" target="_self">Atmospheric Adaptation</a> - The power to instantaneously adjust to any given atmospheric environment. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" target="_self">Air Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate air. INTERMEDIATE LEVEL - As users get to the medium level of air manipulation, their abilities become more refined and versatile. They can generate larger (highly destructive) windstorms and tornadoes and manipulate them with greater control. Users gain the ability to produce more complex air-based attacks, such as airballs, streams of air, or aerokinetic constructs. They can create defensive barriers of air and control the spread of air over a wider area. Additionally, users can enhance the intensity and heat of the wind, allowing them to inflict more damage and exert greater influence over their surroundings. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electricity_Generation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electricity_Generation" target="_self">Electricity Generation</a> - The power to generate electricity.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Sound_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Sound_Manipulation" target="_self">Sound Manipulation</a> -The power to manipulate sound. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electricity_Resistance" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electricity_Resistance" target="_self">Electricity Resistance</a> - The power to be highly resistant to electricity. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electric_Channeling" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electric_Channeling" target="_self">Electric Channeling</a> - The power to channel electricity and use it for a variety of purposes. Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Manipulation" target="_self">Air Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate air. ADVANCED LEVEL - At the master level of air manipulation, users attain mastery over the element of air, unlocking its full potential. They can manipulate air with unlimited skill. Users gain the ability to produce extremely large and extremely powerful winds, capable of engulfing and igniting entire areas or overwhelming multiple opponents simultaneously in the air. They can generate and create massive tornadoes and hurricanes at will and cause very devastating destruction. Users can manipulate the temperature of the wind at will, from searing heat to cold, granting them supernatural control over the superpower of air in most of its forms. In addition to their offensive capabilities. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Pressure_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Pressure_Manipulation" target="_self">Pressure Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate pressure.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Shield_Construction" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Shield_Construction" target="_self">Air Barrier Construction</a> - The ability to create shields out of air.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Oxygen_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Oxygen_Manipulation" target="_self">Oxygen Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate oxygen.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Enhanced_Breath" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Enhanced_Breath" target="_self">Enhanced Breath</a> - The user can exhale gale-force winds or inhale air in order to generate a vortex of wind. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Cutting" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Cutting" target="_self">Air Cutting</a> - The power to use wind to slice apart targets. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Breath_Removal" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Breath_Removal" target="_self">Breath Removal</a> - The power to remove breath of oneself or others.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Weaponry" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Weaponry" target="_self">Air Weaponry</a> - The power to wield or create weapons with air. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Wave_Emission" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Air_Wave_Emission" target="_self">Air Wave Emission</a> - The user can release waves, spirals, rings, pulse, blasts, balls, and bursts of air/wind and use them to damage, push, bind and/or paralyze people. They are able to send wind through any form of matter creating ruptures, and create a pulse that can go through anything, and depending on what the user want it can either be harmful or harmless. Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electrical_Immunity" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Electrical_Immunity" target="_self">Electrical Immunity</a> - The power to be completely unharmed by electricity.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Aeroscience" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Aeroscience" target="_self">Aeroscience</a> - The power to know everything about the air/the winds/gases/skies/vapors/breath/vacuums/weather/the atmospheres. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tactile_Electrokinesis" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tactile_Electrokinesis" target="_self">Tactile Electrokinesis</a> - The power to manipulate electricity through physical contact.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tornado_Creation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Tornado_Creation" target="_self">Tornado Creation</a> - The power to create tornadoes and whirlwinds. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Thunderstorm_Creation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Thunderstorm_Creation" target="_self">Thunderstorm Creation</a> - The power to create a thunderstorm God Unlisted
<br>When the 4 elemental gods combine their power they are granted the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Perfect_Storm" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Perfect_Storm" target="_self">Perfect Storm</a> ability capable of destroy all life on earth. A very powerful user could unleash a storm containing all kinds of natural disasters, including earthquakes, hurricanes, tornado, volcanic eruptions, blizzards etc. causing immense destruction and chaos. Such a storm would be impossible to stop once it started.
Tier 1 - Casual <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Modification" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Modification" target="_self">Body Modification</a> - The user can change and modify the bodies of oneself and others generally for enhancing the physical capabilities, alternating appearances and so on, the modifications can grant certain powers and qualities (be it magical, technological, divine, nature, etc.) that can reach down to genetic or even subatomic levels.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Temperature_Manipulation" target="_self">Body Temperature Manipulation</a> - The ability to manipulate the body temperature of oneself and/or others. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Art_Animation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Art_Animation" target="_self">Body Art Animation</a> - The user can bring their and/or others body art/tattoos to life, manifesting weapons and use whatever illustrations are placed on them as art to materialize. For example, pulling a knife out of a knife tattoo for utility for self-defense purposes.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Language_Analysis" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Language_Analysis" target="_self">Body Language Analysis</a> - The power to intuitively read others' body language and anticipate their actions. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Synchronized_Movement" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Synchronized_Movement" target="_self">Synchronized Movement</a>- The ability to synchronize one's body movement with another to match what their doing. Tier 3 - Professional Sense Manipulation - Manipulate the senses whether one's own or another person's.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Bodyguard_Power" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Bodyguard_Power" target="_self">Bodyguard Power </a>- The power to have a "bodyguard" that takes damage for the user.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Heat_Camouflage" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Heat_Camouflage" target="_self">Body Heat Camouflage</a> - The power to mask one's body heat emissions. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Supremacy" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Supremacy" target="_self">Body Supremacy </a>- The user has complete and total control over one’s bodily capabilities, both biologically (e.g., muscles, bones, veins, neurons, etc.) and systematically (e.g., reflexes, instincts, coordination, psychomotor movement, etc.); being able to move athletically and acrobatically with remarkable grace in conjunction of sustaining a willful enhancement of one's own biological systems to maximize their performance. Tier 4 - Vessel Longevity - Increased lifespan due to preservation of the body/body being maintained in peak condition.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Destruction" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Body_Destruction" target="_self">Body Destruction</a> - The power to easily destroy the body or parts of the body. God Unlisted Tier 1 - Casual <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Telepathy" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Telepathy" target="_self">Telepathy</a> - The psionic ability to read and control the minds and thoughts of humans, animals, and other sentient beings, and to transfer information from one mind to another without the aid of physical communication (noise or movement). <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Enhanced_Memory" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Enhanced_Memory" target="_self">Enhanced Memory</a> - The power to remember and recall experiences and events inhumanly well.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Peak_Human_Mind/Enhanced" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Peak_Human_Mind/Enhanced" target="_self">Enhanced Mind</a> - The user possesses extraordinary mental faculties that far surpass those of their ordinary counterparts. They exhibit heightened intelligence, intuition, creativity, charisma, instinct, and wisdom, as well as a greater brain capacity and deductive skills compared to other members of their species, such as humans. Tier 2 - Hobbyist Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Illusion_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Illusion_Manipulation" target="_self">Illusion Manipulation</a> - Users can manipulate illusions and hallucinations, allowing them to alter the perceptions of others and create entirely fabricated experiences. Illusions are false interpretations of existing stimuli, such as making a small object appear larger or masking a real location by disguising it. Hallucinations, on the other hand, involve creating sensory experiences without any basis in reality, such as making someone see a nonexistent creature, hear imaginary voices, or feel phantom sensations. This power enables users to distort the way targets see, hear, touch, smell, or taste, leading to a variety of deceptive and strategic effects. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psychic_Shield" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psychic_Shield" target="_self">Psychic Shield</a> - The user is highly resistant to any/all mental intrusion, including psychic or empathic powers, Hypnosis, Hallucination Inducement, Memory Manipulation, deception, etc. Telepathy only “hear” static, while mind controllers will have trouble manipulating those shielded.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Telekinesis" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Telekinesis" target="_self">Telekinesis</a> - The power to move, manipulate or otherwise interact with matter/energy without physical means Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Instilled_Knowledge" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Instilled_Knowledge" target="_self">Instilled Knowledge</a> - The power to have knowledge instilled into the mind by various means, rather than acquiring it through studying or experience.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Hive_Mind" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Hive_Mind" target="_self">Hive Mind</a> - The ability to share a collective consciousness between multiple bodies. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Memory_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Memory_Manipulation" target="_self">Memory Manipulation</a> - User can control memories of oneself and others, allowing them to modify, fabricate, suppress, influence, repair, restore, erase, detect, and view them. They can change memories to confuse, or wipe away certain memories to cause amnesia, discern and provoke nostalgia, and enter the victim into a psychic vision, replaying their memory. Mind Control - The user can control the minds of others, including their thoughts, perceptions, behaviours, movements, memories, emotions and personality. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Unconsciousness_Inducement" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Unconsciousness_Inducement" target="_self">Unconsciousness Inducement</a> - The power to induce unconsciousness. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Intuitive_Aptitude" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Intuitive_Aptitude" target="_self">Intuitive Aptitude</a> - The power to intuitively understand the workings of anything no matter how simple or complex. God <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Cosmic_Awareness" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Cosmic_Awareness" target="_self">Cosmic Awareness</a> - The power to be cognizant of goings on across the universe itself. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Intelligence/Absolute" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Intelligence/Absolute" target="_self">Absolute Intelligence</a> - The power to possess a limitless level of intellectual and cognitive proficiency that surpasses anything/everything in existence.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Peak_Human_Mind/Absolute" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Peak_Human_Mind/Absolute" target="_self">Absolute Mind</a> - The power to possess limitless mental attributes and capabilities. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psionic_Inundation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psionic_Inundation" target="_self">Psionic Inundation</a> This ability is a result of the user experiencing moments of extreme stress. Not specific to any tier. The user can mentally overload the brain with psychic energy by mentally inducing and manifesting psychic energy within the brain of those being affected by will alone, causing the victim to spontaneously experience brain damage, memory loss, unconsciousness, vegetative state and/or death. Unlisted Tier 1 - Casual Empathy - The user can fully interpret the emotions, moods, and temperaments of others without reading apparent symptoms, allowing them to understand introverts or discover one emotion is actually hiding another. Aura Reading - Innate ability within all soul affinities that allows the user to see auras of the people around them. Sixth Sense - Ability to see wandering souls on the moral plane. Can see the dead. Tier 2 - Hobbyist <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Summoning" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Summoning" target="_self">Soul Summoning</a> - The power to summon souls from beyond the grave. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Emotion_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Emotion_Manipulation" target="_self">Emotion Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate emotions. Tier 3 - Professional <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Resonation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Resonation" target="_self">Soul Resonation</a> - User can harmonize their soul with other souls, synchronizing and multiplying spiritual strength of all participants. (THE POWER OF FRIENDSHIP)
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Astral_Projection" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Astral_Projection" target="_self">Astral Projection</a> - The power to project the consciousness of oneself from the body. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Dream_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Dream_Manipulation" target="_self">Dream Manipulation</a> - The power to manipulate dreams. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psychic_Shadow" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Psychic_Shadow" target="_self">Psychic Shadow</a> - The ability to mask psychic presence and obscure the perceptions of psychic trackers. <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul-Puppetry" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul-Puppetry" target="_self">Soul Puppetry</a> - The power to contain and preserve one's soul into a single object which remotely controls the body. Ability to control another's soul. Tier 4 - Vessel <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Manipulation" target="_self">Soul Manipulation</a> - Users can freely create, shape, and control the soul/souls. Soul Mutilation Soul Destruction Soul Restoration Soul Removal <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Healing" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Healing" target="_self">Soul Healing</a> - The power to heal damage done to the soul. God <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Manipulation" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Manipulation" target="_self">Soul Manipulation</a> - Users can freely create, shape, and control the soul/souls. Soul Mutilation Soul Destruction Soul Creation Soul Removal <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Splitting" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Splitting" target="_self">Soul Splitting</a> / <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Merging" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Soul_Merging" target="_self">Merging</a> Soul Restoration Soul Healing Unlisted ]]></description><link>03-notes/magic-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Magic Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 01:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Affinities (old)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Water, being so tied to life on the planet itself, is often associated with healing properties. It is versatile—able to change its shape to fit the circumstance. That being said, water can be calm and collected like a stream or violent and unpredictable like a storm.The Kraken - RazzleThe water deity is known for being calm and collected. A storm simmers beneath the surface, and her mysteries remain buried deep. She would prefer to take the path of least resistance, but will not back down from a fight when forced in a corner.Casual Hobbyist Professional Vessel God ]]></description><link>03-notes/affinities-(old).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Affinities (old).md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[character (old)]]></title><link>05-resources/testing/archive/character-(old).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/archive/character (old).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Remnants of Humanity]]></title><description><![CDATA[history of cirrane]]></description><link>00-wiki/history/the-remnants-of-humanity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/History/The Remnants of Humanity.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Dragon's Gauntlet]]></title><link>00-wiki/the-dragon's-gauntlet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/The Dragon's Gauntlet.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:45:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[02 - Tagging System]]></title><description><![CDATA[So What's All This? This is how tags should be organized
When a new note is created in a folder a template will be created with premade tags
All tags are nested by group #status A way to track progress #status/draft: Rough drafts
#status/revising: Tweaking drafts
#status/complete: Page is all done!
#status/in-progress: For pages being actively worked on #groups and #stories
Characters involved in certain groups and stories (ie. triad, labs, etc)
example of a group tag: #groups/temple-of-lux/characters Group Tagging #groups/group-name: the group #groups/group-name/characters: members of that group Story Tagging #stories/story-name: name of story #stories/overview: summary of the story
#stories/story-name/characters: characters within that story
#stories/story-name/notes: messy notes and word vomit
#stories/story-name/outline: outlines
#stories/story-name/script: written scripts #stories/story-name/script/scenes: different scenes within script ##stories/story-name/timeline #locations: locations of note #locations/location-name #locations/location-name/residents
#locations/location-name/notes
#locations/location-name/organizations #characters: Character Profiles
Use story and group tags on character pages to categorize them #characters/major: main characters
#characters/secondary: important side characters
#characters/minor: characters that appear less frequently
#characters/bg: characters that are set dressing
#characters/affinity #characters/affinity/water
#characters/affinity/fire
#characters/affinity/air
#characters/affinity/earth
#characters/affinity/body
#characters/affinity/mind
#characters/affinity/soul #magic
#magic/water
#magic/fire
#magic/air
#magic/earth
#magic/body
#magic/mind
#magic/soul ]]></description><link>06-guides-&amp;-to-do/02-tagging-system.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">06 - Guides &amp; To-Do/02 - Tagging System.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[99 - Github Pages]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Export as HTML
Online Website
Warning
No files over 100mb!! Create repo
Command line:
- init
- git remote add origin
- git add --all
- git push Go to Settings
Go to Pages Source: Deploy from branch
Branch: Main -&gt; docs/ Save
]]></description><link>06-guides-&amp;-to-do/99-github-pages.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">06 - Guides &amp; To-Do/99 - Github Pages.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[00 - To Do]]></title><description><![CDATA[To Do Outlines The Journalist (In Progress)
The Engineer
Mystic Hues
The Pheonix Templates Character Template
Timeline Template
Outline Template
Roleplay Template Other Prepare doc for bases update
Transfer information to Needs Name Mountain
Region
Districts
Gauntlets
Gods
Lake at the bottom of Esterra ]]></description><link>06-guides-&amp;-to-do/00-to-do.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">06 - Guides &amp; To-Do/00 - To Do.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:38:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[01 - How to Use]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Use source view to edit.
Use reading view to display the page as intended
In the top right corner is a menu. This will open up a panel for editing properties. This is essential for editing basic information on character pages Obsidian works a lot like Wikipedia [[Link]]: Links to other pages.
![[Image.png]]: Displays an image [[Page#Heading]]: Links a heading on that page. Formating &gt; blockquotes
- lists &gt; [!] Title callouts (fancy blockquotes) Creating notes in the correct folder will generate the relevant template including tags and metadata. DO NOT COPY PASTE TEMPLATES <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/r-u-s-h-i-k-e-s-h/Obsidian-CSS-Snippets/tree/Collection" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/r-u-s-h-i-k-e-s-h/Obsidian-CSS-Snippets/tree/Collection" target="_self">Snippet Gallery</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/efemkay/obsidian-modular-css-layout/tree/main" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/efemkay/obsidian-modular-css-layout/tree/main" target="_self">Modular CSS Layout</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Colored-Sidebar" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Colored-Sidebar" target="_self">Colored Sidebar</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Vault-Template/blob/main/Vault/.obsidian/snippets/CyanVoxel's%20General%20Tweaks.css" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Vault-Template/blob/main/Vault/.obsidian/snippets/CyanVoxel's%20General%20Tweaks.css" target="_self">CyanVoxel's General Tweaks</a>
]]></description><link>06-guides-&amp;-to-do/01-how-to-use.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">06 - Guides &amp; To-Do/01 - How to Use.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Da Colors]]></title><description><![CDATA[WOMP
hehehehehe HOHOHO ⬤ rosewater ⬤ flamingo ⬤ pink ⬤ mauve ⬤ red ⬤ maroon ⬤ peach ⬤ yellow ⬤ green ⬤ teal ⬤ sky ⬤ sapphire ⬤ blue ⬤ lavender ⬤ text ⬤ subtext1 ⬤ subtext0 ⬤ overlay2 ⬤ overlay1 ⬤ overlay0 ⬤ surface2 ⬤ surface1 ⬤ surface0 ⬤ base ⬤ mantle ⬤ crust ]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/da-colors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/Da Colors.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[lists]]></title><description><![CDATA[major1 resultSort0Filter0PropertiesNewFjFjFjFjfile namecharacter]]></description><link>05-resources/bases/lists.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Bases/lists.base</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 00:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Test Zone]]></title><description><![CDATA[WOW
dont die
Infobox <img alt="cover hsmall" src="05-resources/images/icons/celeste.png" target="_self"> Main paragraph contentBlank container <br>list 1 <a href=".?query=tag:mcl/list-column" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#mcl/list-column">#mcl/list-column</a>
list 2
list 3
list 4 Next paragraph contentInfo
Addition note to the main article
Page Types
character affiliations timeline
templates
outline
notes
scripts
Categories<br><a data-href="How to Use#^story" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">How to Use &gt; ^story</a>Dataview: No results to show for table query.major1 resultSort0Filter0PropertiesNewFjFjFjFj]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/test-zone.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/Test Zone.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 00:57:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="docs/05-resources/images/icons/celeste.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="docs/05-resources/images/icons/celeste.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[character-v2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ list of nicknames used for links %%"
cssclasses:
chara
wide
wide-tabs
tags:
character
"#character/major"
image: "![[cafelogobig.png]]"
age: 0
birthday: Month 00th
gender: ♀/♂/⚲ (pro/noun)
sexuality: Sexuality
occupation: Job
affiliates:
- "[[group]]"
- "[[group]]"
- "[[group]]"
height: 0'0"
affinity: Affinity
nationality: Nationality
creator: Creator
quote: Something your funny guy would say Relationship 01 %%Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. <br>Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. [[character]]: Relation
[[character]]: Relation
[[character]]: Relation
-Dataview: No results to show for list query.]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/archive/character-v2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/archive/character-v2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[character-v3]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chara Multi column
Img
- Desc
Blockquote
❝ - ❞ PersonalityTriviaMannerismsBlockquote
adjective • adjective • adjective Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Pos Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Pos Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Pos Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Neg Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Neg Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Neg Trait: Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet Random
Facts About
Them
Multi column
Speech Patterns Habit
Habit
Habit Examples Ex
Ex
Ex Body Language Thing
Thing
Thing No-Nos
Things they would never do Thing
Thing Thing Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character-v3]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. <br>Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character-v3]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. [[character-v3]]: Relation
[[character-v3]]: Relation
[[character-v3]]: Relation
-Dataview: No results to show for list query.]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/archive/character-v3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/archive/character-v3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:43:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[character-v4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Infobox
-
- • - • - Blockquote
"Something your funny guy would say" Age -
Birthday -
Height -
Affinity -
Nationality -
Creator - - -
Blockquote
adjective • adjective • adjective
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. pos trait
pos trait
pos trait neg trait
neg trait
neg trait
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character-v3]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. <br>Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
[[character-v3]] [Relation] - Quote Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. - [[character]]: Relation
- [[character]]: Relation
- [[character]]: RelationDataview: No results to show for list query.]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/archive/character-v4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/archive/character-v4.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:42:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[testzone...2!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Infobox <img alt="cover hsmall" src="05-resources/images/icons/celeste.png" target="_self"> <br>This is a simple footnote<a data-footref="1" href="#fn-1-7aa89b7c58985dfd" class="footnote-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">[1]</a>.<br>
chara <a data-footref="eee" href="#fn-2-7aa89b7c58985dfd" class="footnote-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">[2]</a><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="How to Use > ^test" data-href="How to Use#^test" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Test</a>= this.test <br>This is the referenced text.<a href="#fnref-1-7aa89b7c58985dfd" class="footnote-backref footnote-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">↩︎</a>
Add 2 spaces at the start of each new line.<br>
This lets you write footnotes that span multiple lines.<a href="#fnref-2-7aa89b7c58985dfd" class="footnote-backref footnote-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">↩︎</a>
]]></description><link>05-resources/testing/testzone...2!.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Testing/testzone...2!.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:34:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[cafelogobig]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/cafelogobig.png</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 14:31:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Github Pages]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Export as HTML
Online Website
Warning
No files over 100mb!! Create repo
Command line:
- init
- git remote add origin
- git add --all
- git push Go to Settings
Go to Pages Source: Deploy from branch
Branch: Main -&gt; docs/ Save
]]></description><link>05-resources/guides-&amp;-resources/github-pages.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Guides &amp; Resources/Github Pages.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cirrane]]></title><description><![CDATA[From highest to lowest
Horizon District
- Politicians
- Rich and Famous
- The dome
- Home of Dragon's Gauntlet
- Characters of Note
- Matcha
- Ched
- Magical Pressurized Dome Fourth District
- Upper Class
- Commercial District
- Less residential
- Apartments
- Mind and Body Gauntlet Gauntlet Third District
- Residential
- Suburbs
- Parks
- Small forests
- Deep Creekish
- Cirrane High
- Highest Amount of:
- Hospitals
- Doctors offices
- Population
- Characters of Note:
- Taro/Bonbon
- The Crew
- Rudy/Aubrey Second District
- Touristy area
- Resorts
- Hotels
- Museums
- Water and Fire Gauntlet
- Characters of Note
- Inko/Deacon
- Cherry/Pom
- Percy
- Azalea First District Contains Gullywash
Seaport
Industrial
Warehouses
Import/Exports
Trades and Goods
Air and Earth Gauntlet Martini (5th)
Gyokuro (4th)
Rosemary (3rd)
Pop (?) (2nd)
Brie (1st)
District Name Brainstorm
Sun
Star
Moon
Horizon Melting Pot
Origin of the gauntlet
Located on a mountainside (Mount name not decided)
Top district home of the hollywood elite
rich people
famous people Home of innovation, science and research They value STEM programs*
Lots of revisionist history
There is a bomb in the middle of the city (aka god aka finding nemo)
Customs center around the Dragon's Gauntlet Dragon Festival (Nov) Love of artistry Trains are most common. Fast like a bullet train.
Aircrafts land on the country side Between Skye Valley and Cirrane, after the bridge
A bullet train rides people into the city Helipads are common in district 4th
Bikes are encouraged
Cars exist, not used super frequent
Hoverboards are popular Countryside
Located outside the city
Doesn't belong to one specific district
Home to the air god Knowledge is lost to time
lots of imagery of flight
Old World Residence for those who worshipped Pavana Fest in his name
Four Winds fest (?)
Then there was a massacre and they all died
and pavana hates people
Tradition continues today but roots are lost to time Secrets stay secrets in the valley
people with shady backgrounds restart their lives
They protect their own
Rural Farmlands
Produce
Textiles
Exports go to the city Have their own dialect (northerner accents) Boston
Little bit of a southern fusion in there
no i dont know what that sounds like but imagine
Spea### References <img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/mountainwater.png" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane2.png" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane.png" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self">king with new england accent
- Uses southern terminology]]></description><link>03-notes/locations/cirrane.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Locations/Cirrane.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:06:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="docs/05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/mountainwater.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="docs/05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/mountainwater.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Esterra]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Mining colony that gained their independence from Cirrane The Mines: In the deepest depths of Esterra, resides a cavern of crystals that can hold magical charges. The working conditions suck
The crystals are monitored by the government, any unmarked crystals are considered illegal!! Most people bilingual Derivative of common language
Real World Accent not known...yet Food Lots of earthy veggies
Mostly known for stews, vibrant veggie dishes, and unique spices Communing with Nature Moon It is believed Esterra was formed after the earth god launched a large piece of earth into the sky creating the second moon. Earth Religion A belief that all things return to the earth and it should be honored
Traditional prayer involves incense and candles, they burn sage to cleanse areas such as new homes/businesses/etc. Esterrans have a day where they celebrate the dead Lanterns with letters, prayers and pictures are sent into the sky to be gifted to their departed loved ones.
The holiday is always on a the second moon's full moon (idk which month yet) Should be during fall/autumn when the veil between the land of the living and dead is at its thinnest Mourning the Dead Private prayers are written on paper and burned so the embers can carry their messages to the dead
All things return to earth Esterrans believe that all things return to the earth, the living included. Their funerals are centered around this belief. When a person dies, their body is returned to the earth from which it came. The body is placed in a bed of flowers where it will remain until moving on to its final resting place. A family member will be tasked with traveling to the lake to retrieve a Lily of the Moon. The lily is believed to contain the essence of the dead who will help guide their loved one into the afterlife. After the funeral, the body will be moved to a botanical cemetery (found throughout Esterra) where it will then stay until they have returned to the earth (become compost), at which point the soil will be collected and sent down to the lake to fertilize the Lily of the Moon. Thus the cycle repeats itself! Keepers of the Lily Organization tasked with maintaining the Lily of the Moon and assisting with its cultivation and growth
Keepers of the Lily are exclusively soul affinities, to be chosen as one of them is viewed as a great honor
They live at the lake and dedicate their lives to the lily It's located in a giant crater created by Gaia during the great calamity
Buildings line the rim and spiral deeper into the crater.
A lake sits at the bottom Folklore about a monster!?
There's a purification center that provides water for the citizens
Home to the Lily of the Moon - Special flower that can only grow along the lake The deepest part of the crater is dangerous Need equipment to safely traverse
Uneven terrain
Slippery terrain
Toxic gases
A m-m-monster!?
Drowning
Low oxygen More of a problem in small tunnels and enclosures The lowest inhabitable zone Ventilation
Water is filtered, but not perfect
Home of most mining operations Esterra's military was born about from a need to gain independence from Cirrane. They still exist today They regulate da crystals
You gotta serve for like five years
Propaganda!?
why DOES the military exist, HMMMMM
<img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/960px-nördlingendanielblicksüden.html" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/noerdlingen-sehenswuerdigkeiten-01.webp" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/j8ugsjybugp3z2mcfjtcle.webp" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/5fdd66360044a.webp" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/4b.webp" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self"><img src="05-resources/images/galleries/esterra/1200px-hohokam_cliff_dwelling_(montezuma_castle)%2c_arizona.html" style="border-radius: 0px;" target="_self">]]></description><link>03-notes/locations/esterra.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Locations/Esterra.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:05:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Other Locations]]></title><description><![CDATA[n
- The dead are placed in a sacred burial site where their bodies become one with the earth and provide enrichment to the soil so that the Lily of the Moon may grow
Siren's Bay: British Isles (water) Volin: France
Akiatori: Japan (fire)
]]></description><link>03-notes/locations/other-locations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - Notes/Locations/Other Locations.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 21:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[cafebg]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/cafebg.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/cafebg.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/cafebg.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:41:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cirrane2]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane2.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Galleries/Cirrane/cirrane2.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:40:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[lingxiang1982_207090_1162215133_orig]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/lingxiang1982_207090_1162215133_orig.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/lingxiang1982_207090_1162215133_orig.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/lingxiang1982_207090_1162215133_orig.jpg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:03:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[thumb-1920-35819]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/thumb-1920-35819.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/thumb-1920-35819.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/thumb-1920-35819.jpg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[chigu_12_DnChpCMU4AAi2fu]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/chigu_12_dnchpcmu4aai2fu.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/chigu_12_dnchpcmu4aai2fu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/chigu_12_DnChpCMU4AAi2fu.jpg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:38:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backgrounds-Anime-Landscape-Download]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/backgrounds-anime-landscape-download.jpg" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/backgrounds-anime-landscape-download.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/Backgrounds-Anime-Landscape-Download.jpg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:28:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cloudmountain]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/banners/cloudmountain.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/banners/cloudmountain.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Banners/cloudmountain.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:38:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Do]]></title><description><![CDATA[To Do Outlines The Journalist (In Progress)
The Engineer
Mystic Hues
The Pheonix Templates Character Template
Timeline Template
Outline Template
Roleplay Template Other Prepare doc for bases update
Transfer information to Needs Name Mountain
Region
Districts
Gauntlets
Gods
Lake at the bottom of Esterra ]]></description><link>05-resources/guides-&amp;-resources/to-do.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Guides &amp; Resources/To Do.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[groups]]></title><description><![CDATA[characters1 resultSort0Filter1PropertiesNewFjFjFjFjfile namecharacter]]></description><link>05-resources/bases/groups.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Bases/groups.base</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Journalist]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.)Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.stories1 resultSort0Filter1PropertiesNewFjFjFjFj]]></description><link>01-stories/the-journalist/the-journalist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/The Journalist/The Journalist.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[character]]></title><description><![CDATA[Infobox
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self">
0 • ♀/♂/⚲ (pro/noun) • 0'0" Blockquote
❝ Something your funny guy would say ❞ Age 0
Birthday Month 00th
Height 0'0"
Affinity Affinity
Nationality Nationality
Creator Creator <br><a data-href="affiliate" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">affiliate</a>
<br><a data-href="affiliate" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">affiliate</a>
<br><a data-href="affiliate" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">affiliate</a> <br><a data-href="chara" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">chara</a>
<br><a data-href="chara" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">chara</a>
<br><a data-href="chara" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">chara</a> Blockquote
adjective • adjective • adjective
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. pos trait
pos trait
pos trait neg trait
neg trait
neg trait
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.<br>Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
<a data-href="character" href="05-resources/templates/character.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">character</a> [Relation] - ❝ Quote❞ Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. <br>Col
R img
<img alt="cafelogobig.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/cafelogobig.png" target="_self"> R desc
<a data-href="character" href="05-resources/templates/character.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">character</a> [Relation] - ❝ Quote❞ Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. <br><a data-href="character" href="05-resources/templates/character.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">character</a>: Relation
<br><a data-href="character" href="05-resources/templates/character.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">character</a>: Relation
<br><a data-href="character" href="05-resources/templates/character.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">character</a>: Relation
stories-chara1 resultSort0Filter2PropertiesNewfile nameblurb]]></description><link>05-resources/templates/character.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Templates/character.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:22:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Outline]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Kiwi has interviewed Tequila a few times for a yearly review. Tequila gathered intel on Kiwi for the first interview.
Tequlia conducts background checks on all press coverage to insure there are no bad actors.
All people who interact with the governor are kept on file. Morelle moves to Cirrane a few years after Kiwi's departure. Got bored of her work life and wanted something new. Held hope that maybe Kiwi is in Cirrane somewhere.
Couldn't find him because Cirrane is so huge and foreign to her. Ethereal Shadows gains traction in the sports scene. big time Kiwi reconnects with Morelle everything is sunshine and roses and happy times
Kenny is pouty because Morelle is spending all her time with Kiwi. Kiwi tells Morelle about the book he wants to write. It's a good chance for him to build his portfolio and get his name out there. Kiwi starts the interviewing Tequila. Tequila starts asking questions about Kiwi after interview sessions.
Kiwi is not comfortable with talking about his past because he defected from the Esterran army and he may be forced to return.
Tequila promises nothing will happen to him and offers him a job.
He reluctantly accepts after some hemming and hawing. He asks for information about the crystals.
She promises to give clearance, but it will take a while. Morelle and Kiwi are concerned about Tequila Why does she know that Kiwi defected from the army?
Why bring it up?
What does she plan to do with that information. Tims are subservient to Kiwi and help him feel welcomed in his new office. They drive him crazy
He hates them
Oh my god. Martini comes in and calls Kiwi "Tim". He hates it.
Mentions it to Tequila. Martini is summoned to Tequila's office Tequila tells Martini to treat Kiwi with respect
Martini is annoyed about it but she goes along with it After a few weeks of working, Kiwi feels someone attempting to read his mind. Mind affinities can only read the thoughts of someone nearby. A room away at maximum The only people who cross paths with him frequently are the Tims.
Martini could also be a possibility.
Tequila, who's a mind vessel, is able to hone in on people at longer distances.
She uses Martini to manipulate Kiwi's feelings and make him feel safe.
She's surprised Kiwi is able to keep her out, it's not often that people can do that.
She becomes interested in him.
This happens off and on for a few weeks. Kiwi comes home and tells Morelle about what happened. The two of them are concerned.
Morelle suggests he reports on it. Kiwi reports to Tequila that someone is reading his mind That's a big security concern.
She says they will investigate and narrow down who's responsible.
Tequila sends Lima to give Kiwi papers.
Kiwi feels someone getting into his head again. At a later date, Lima passes Kiwi's room. Kiwi feels someone in his head.
He starts to think it's Lima.
Tequila picks up on this. Kiwi goes to the cafe where Lima is nearby. Someone is in his head again.
Outside of work.
He tells Morelle he's certain it's Lima.
Neither of them know Lima's affinity. Trinity Affinities are subtle and harder to notice. He could be a mind affinity...right? They don't have hard proof though... Kiwi tells Tequila that he thinks Lima is behind it.
She says they will look into it.
Lima is gone from that point on.
Kiwi still feels someone getting into his head outside of work though...
He starts avoiding Cafeccino Tequila "fires" Lima Says he's making Kiwi uncomfortable.
She's moving him downstairs.
He's like "Uh why? What the hell?" but just goes with it. Tequila amps up Kiwi's workload More meetings
More paperworks
More articles
This happens gradually over time.
Press Journalist was fired, Kiwi takes over the job It's articles about magical shipments. Keeps promising him clearance. Kiwi starts working overtime. Stays after work
Comes home late
Feels burnt out all the time
Some days he can't remember what he did
etc Morelle becomes concerned for Kiwi's wellbeing and suggests he takes time off Kiwi refuses the first time
Kiwi falls asleep at the desk Tequila calls his emergency contact (Morelle) and requests that she picks him up.
Morelle tells Kiwi to please take time off
Kiwi finally accepts and ask Tequila for time off
Tequila agrees. He can't work his best if hes not well rested.
She's so nice :) Kiwi takes a break and comes back to work with a fresh mind But workload never ceases.
There's even MORE work to be done. Lima is engineering something that can be used to make workers more complicit Puts a mental block
block memories and certain emotions
Struggling to get it right
Wants Tequila's approval
But also doesnt want to complete the project because what if she uses it against him?
Tries to design something to counteract it so he can protect himself and Rita
??? The experiment backfires Messes with Kiwi
Creates gaps in his memory
Tequila upset that Lima is messing up her project
Tells him to fix it
He's given a short amount of time to fix it The experiment backfires again in a worse way Kiwi passes out at work
He's seemingly unresponsive Tequila tells lima that if he can't be useful as an engineer then he can at least show his worth as a soldier
Has him train for assassin work instead
then asked with attacking the cafe
if he's trained correctly, he should have no qualms about killing people he knows Kiwi lands in the hospital for a day or two Tequila tells him to take two weeks off
Morelle wants Kiwi to quit
Kiwi puts in his two weeks notice upon returning to work
Tequila saids thats a shame because his clearance was almost ready It wasnt but she gets Martini to accelerate the process Kiwi can't resist knowledge, he stays His clearance comes through in two weeks
Morelle is worried....... ]]></description><link>01-stories/the-journalist/outlines-&amp;-notes/outline.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/The Journalist/Outlines &amp; Notes/Outline.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[location]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blurb about the location. This will be listed in <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="internal-link" href=".html" data-href="List of locations" target="_self">List of locations</a>. Use the &lt;br&gt; tag if the blurb has a line break.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.
characters1 resultSort0Filter1PropertiesNewFjFjFjFj
]]></description><link>05-resources/templates/location.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Templates/location.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Use]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Use source view to edit.
Use reading view to display the page as intended
In the top right corner is a menu. This will open up a panel for editing properties. This is essential for editing basic information on character pages Obsidian works a lot like Wikipedia [[Link]]: Links to other pages.
![[Image.png]]: Displays an image [[Page#Heading]]: Links a heading on that page. Formating &gt; blockquotes
- lists &gt; [!] Title callouts (fancy blockquotes) Creating notes in the correct folder will generate the relevant template including tags and metadata. DO NOT COPY PASTE TEMPLATES <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/r-u-s-h-i-k-e-s-h/Obsidian-CSS-Snippets/tree/Collection" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/r-u-s-h-i-k-e-s-h/Obsidian-CSS-Snippets/tree/Collection" target="_self">Snippet Gallery</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/efemkay/obsidian-modular-css-layout/tree/main" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/efemkay/obsidian-modular-css-layout/tree/main" target="_self">Modular CSS Layout</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Colored-Sidebar" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Colored-Sidebar" target="_self">Colored Sidebar</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Vault-Template/blob/main/Vault/.obsidian/snippets/CyanVoxel's%20General%20Tweaks.css" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/CyanVoxel/Obsidian-Vault-Template/blob/main/Vault/.obsidian/snippets/CyanVoxel's%20General%20Tweaks.css" target="_self">CyanVoxel's General Tweaks</a>
]]></description><link>05-resources/guides-&amp;-resources/how-to-use.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Guides &amp; Resources/How to Use.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tagging System]]></title><description><![CDATA[So What's All This? This is how tags should be organized
When a new note is created in a folder a template will be created with premade tags
All tags are nested by group #status A way to track progress #status/draft: Rough drafts
#status/revising: Tweaking drafts
#status/complete: Page is all done!
#status/in-progress: For pages being actively worked on #groups and #stories
Characters involved in certain groups and stories (ie. triad, labs, etc)
example of a group tag: #groups/temple-of-lux/characters Group Tagging #groups/group-name: the group #groups/group-name/characters: members of that group Story Tagging #stories/story-name: name of story #stories/overview: summary of the story
#stories/story-name/characters: characters within that story
#stories/story-name/notes: messy notes and word vomit
#stories/story-name/outline: outlines
#stories/story-name/script: written scripts #stories/story-name/script/scenes: different scenes within script ##stories/story-name/timeline #locations: locations of note #locations/location-name #locations/location-name/residents
#locations/location-name/notes
#locations/location-name/organizations #characters: Character Profiles
Use story and group tags on character pages to categorize them #characters/major: main characters
#characters/secondary: important side characters
#characters/minor: characters that appear less frequently
#characters/bg: characters that are set dressing
#characters/affinity #characters/affinity/water
#characters/affinity/fire
#characters/affinity/air
#characters/affinity/earth
#characters/affinity/body
#characters/affinity/mind
#characters/affinity/soul #magic
#magic/water
#magic/fire
#magic/air
#magic/earth
#magic/body
#magic/mind
#magic/soul ]]></description><link>05-resources/guides-&amp;-resources/tagging-system.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Guides &amp; Resources/Tagging System.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[affinity]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img alt="Bonbon.png" src="05-resources/images/icons/bonbon.png" target="_self">yeah]]></description><link>05-resources/templates/affinity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Templates/affinity.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 21:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[group]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blurb about the group. This will be listed in <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="internal-link" href=".html" data-href="List of Groups" target="_self">List of Groups</a>. Use the &lt;br&gt; tag if the blurb has a line break.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.characters1 resultSort0Filter1PropertiesNewFjFjFjFj]]></description><link>05-resources/templates/group.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Templates/group.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 21:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Locations]]></title><description><![CDATA[
The City of Innovation <a data-href="Cirrane" href="03-notes/locations/cirrane.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cirrane</a> is a large city built into the summit of Mount [Name]. It's known as the great mixing pot of [Region]. It has a dense population with buildings winding to the peak. The city is most famous for the <a data-href="Dragon's Gauntlet" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon's Gauntlet</a>, a regional sport popularized centuries prior. A Place to go when you have a latte on your plate.
<br>
<a data-href="B. Scotti" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">B. Scotti</a> loved quiet mornings and a fresh cup of coffee. Migrating from Esterra, B. Scotti wanted to create a home away from home, a safe space for Esterrans migrating to Cirrane. His little cafe would grow and more and more locals gathered to have B. Scotti’s iconic coffee. Now the cafe is inhabited with folks from all different walks of life. Locals sing the praises of <a data-href="Cafeccino" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cafeccino</a>, a place to go when you have a latte on your plate. A short walk from Cafeccino, there is an airstream trailer that has been converted into an ice cream stand. This is where Nilla Vanille owns and operates the making of Inkopolis's creamiest concoctions. Thanks to her fathers Rocky and Rhodes, she has positioned the stand in a prime location: in front of the cafe, where her treats pair perfectly with the drinks to be found inside, and a short walk from where weary gauntlet runners can celebrate victories and soften losses with a delicious ice cream. She is always experimenting with inventing new flavors, and much of her extra income is spent in the form of donations to (????), of which she is very vocal about. <br>
Tucked away in an alley down the concrete stairs sits Kerplunk. Wayward souls and tired commuters stop by to drown away their sorrows in alcoholic ecstasy. The wild, the angry, the bitter, all gathered in one place like a perverted symphony. <a data-href="Corsair" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Corsair</a>, the bartender, reveled in the chaos. This fast talking, wise cracking woman has a penchant for trouble, and welcomes it with open (fire)arms. Those with more dubious intentions sought out Kerplunk’s secret menu: brandy with a side of…illegal weaponry!? The Remnants of God's Wrath
<br>
<a data-href="Esterra" href="03-notes/locations/esterra.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Esterra</a> is a city located inside a deep canyon. Esterra and Cirrane have a history rife with fighting over resources. As resources began to diminish within the small nation, however, Esterra decided to enter into a tentative treaty with Cirrane and end all disputes. The treaty turned a formerly closed border nation into one open to tourism.
Blue Ridge Summit
]]></description><link>00-wiki/locations/locations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Locations/Locations.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Untitled 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blurb about the group. This will be listed in <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="internal-link" href=".html" data-href="List of Groups" target="_self">List of Groups</a>. Use the &lt;br&gt; tag if the blurb has a line break.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Dataview: No results to show for table query.]]></description><link>00-wiki/groups/untitled-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Groups/Untitled 1.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 01:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[mountainwater]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/mountainwater.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/mountainwater.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Galleries/Cirrane/mountainwater.png</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:12:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notes]]></title><link>01-stories/the-journalist/outlines-&amp;-notes/notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/The Journalist/Outlines &amp; Notes/Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:06:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Script]]></title><link>01-stories/the-journalist/script-&amp;-scenes/script.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/The Journalist/Script &amp; Scenes/Script.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blurb about the group. This will be listed in <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="internal-link" href=".html" data-href="List of Groups" target="_self">List of Groups</a>. Use the &lt;br&gt; tag if the blurb has a line break.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.Dataview: No results to show for table query.]]></description><link>00-wiki/groups/untitled.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Groups/Untitled.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[cirrane]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/galleries/cirrane/cirrane.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Galleries/Cirrane/cirrane.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 19:39:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[00 - Example Timeline]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mar 2023Content
“some other notes” is not created yet. Click to create.Jan 2024More content hereMar 2024Content
“some other notes” is not created yet. Click to create.]]></description><link>02-timelines/00-example-timeline.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">02 - Timelines/00 - Example Timeline.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[
The teams gear up for the upcoming tournament.
Showcases the relationship between Mystic Hues and Ethereal Shadows
Stew becomes angry enough that he crafts a plan to rig one of the traps.
It goes horribly wrong taro breaks a leg
aubrey loses an arm
kenny gets roughed up Mystic Hues Taro
Rudy
Percy (?) Ethereal Shadows Stew
Morelle
Bonbon Mystic Hues Matcha
Aubrey
Azalea Ethereal Shadows Kenny
Rose
Acai ]]></description><link>01-stories/the-curse/notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/The Curse/Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Affinities]]></title><description><![CDATA[Water, being so tied to life on the planet itself, is often associated with healing properties. It is versatile—able to change its shape to fit the circumstance. That being said, water can be calm and collected like a stream or violent and unpredictable like a storm.The Kraken - RazzleThe water deity is known for being calm and collected. A storm simmers beneath the surface, and her mysteries remain buried deep. She would prefer to take the path of least resistance, but will not back down from a fight when forced in a corner.Casual Hobbyist Professional Vessel God ]]></description><link>00-wiki/magic/affinities.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Magic/Affinities.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 23:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[elementals]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/infographics/elementals.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/infographics/elementals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Infographics/elementals.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:11:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[trinity]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/infographics/trinity.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/infographics/trinity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Infographics/trinity.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:08:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zola]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/zola.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/zola.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Zola.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[wulfesh]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/wulfesh.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/wulfesh.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/wulfesh.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weiss]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/weiss.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/weiss.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Weiss.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tewkes]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/tewkes.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/tewkes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Tewkes.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taro]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/taro.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/taro.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Taro.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spritzer]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/spritzer.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/spritzer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Spritzer.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rudy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/rudy.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/rudy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Rudy.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pop]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/pop.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/pop.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Pop.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pom]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/pom.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/pom.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Pom.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pita]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/pita.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/pita.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Pita.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papaya]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/papaya.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/papaya.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Papaya.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nilla]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/nilla.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/nilla.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Nilla.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mustard]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/mustard.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/mustard.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Mustard.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MrX]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/mrx.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/mrx.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/MrX.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maple]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/maple.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/maple.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Maple.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Karashi]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/karashi.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/karashi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Karashi.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ginger]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/ginger.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/ginger.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Ginger.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flicka]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/flicka.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/flicka.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Flicka.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fizz]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/fizz.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/fizz.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Fizz.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deacon]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/deacon.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/deacon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Deacon.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Corsair]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/corsair.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/corsair.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Corsair.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ClemS3]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/clems3.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/clems3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/ClemS3.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cherry]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/cherry.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/cherry.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Cherry.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ched]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/ched.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/ched.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Ched.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bonbon]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/bonbon.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/bonbon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Bonbon.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inko]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/inko.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/inko.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/Inko.png</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:06:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Characters]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dataview: No results to show for table query.]]></description><link>00-wiki/characters.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Wiki/Characters.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 03:03:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[celeste]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="05-resources/images/icons/celeste.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>05-resources/images/icons/celeste.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Resources/Images/Icons/celeste.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 03:50:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="."&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Story Navigation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="01 - Stories/The Journalist/The Journalist.md" data-href="01 - Stories/The Journalist/The Journalist.md" href="01-stories/the-journalist/the-journalist.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Journalist</a>: -]]></description><link>01-stories/story-navigation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Stories/Story Navigation.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 19:59:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>